JUSTIN BROWN

justinbrowncodes.github.io | justinjbrown23@gmail.com

Summary

Skilled AI/ML Engineer with a strong background in programming and mathematics. Experienced in exploratory data analysis, statistics, linear algebra, data cleaning, optimizing machine learning models, and evaluating through various metrics. Motivated to collaborate with team members and optimize systems to meet specifications. Proficient in presenting data/concepts clearly and creatively.

Skills

- Numpy, Pandas
- Scikit-Learn, Keras
- Tensorflow, Pytorch
- Matplotlib, Seaborn

- Python
- MatLab
- C++ / Java
- HTML/CSS

- Git version control
- Unix
- Jupyter Notebooks
- SQL

Experience

Lab Technician FSU Department of Biology (Bangi Lab)

12/2020 to Present

Tallahassee, FL

 Performed exploratory analysis on tumor growth data, provided crucial insight for efficient induction procedures for upcoming experiments.

Software Developer

08/2018 to 03/2020

FSU Program in Neuroscience (Vincis Lab)

Tallahassee, FL

- Utilized MATLAB and Python to program neuroscience software for controlling experiments.
- Implemented deep learning models to estimate pupil dilation, reduced the need for other costly methods for collecting neural activity.
- Worked with Principle Investigator to plan, code, and present projects from start to finish.
- Modified lab website to update profiles and implement different API's.

Certifications

• IBM AI Engineering Professional (IBM)

2020

Advanced Machine Learning and Signal Processing

2020

Python Data Structures

2020

Education

Computer Science, Physics, Mathematics

2015-2019

Florida State University

Tallahassee, FL

High School Diploma

2015

Suncoast Community High School

Riviera Beach, FL

• Completed professional development of Android Applications in Java

Extracurricular Activities

FSU Cell and Molecular Biology Graduate Student Association

April 2020

- Developed and Led presentation: "Intro to Neural Networks: Machine Learning with Python".
- Explained process of a neural network and demonstrated the A.I. using a self-made game.

Kaggle 2020-21

Submitted machine learning solutions to complex data science projects.

TechNole 2017 to 2018

Competed in MLH (Major League Hacking) competitions at FSU and Georgia Tech.